My name's Conan Edogawa!
اسمي إيدوغاوا كونان
High school student Shinichi was forced to take a pill that shrunk him!
أُجبر الطالب في الثانوية كودو شينتشي على تجرّع عقار قلّص جسده
Doesn't matter if I'm small!
لا يهمّ صغر بنيتي
My mind is that of a former great detective,
،فعقلي عقل مُتحرٍّ سابق عظيم
and my powers of deduction are flawless
ومهاراتي في الاستنتاج دقيقة
when it comes to cases that seem absolutely unsolvable!
!عندما يتعلق الأمر بالقضايا المستعصية
Valentine's Day is a case of love.
لدينا قضيّة حُب في يوم الفالنتاين
Who knows, there may be poison in that sweet chocolate!
قد يكون هناك سُم في الشوكولاتة الحلوة
So, what are you going to do, Ran?
ماذا ستفعلين إذاً يا ران؟
About what?
بخصوص ماذا؟
Your chocolate for Valentine's Day!
!الشوكولاتة! ليوم الفالنتاين
This huge event only comes once a year, you know!
!الحدث الكبير الذي يأتي مرّةً في العام
We have to use chocolate to capture men's hearts!
!علينا استعمال الشوكولاتة لأسر قلوب الرجال
Oh, right...
...أ-أجل
You're, like, spacing out or something...
كأنّك شاردة الذهن
Am I?
ماذا؟ حقّاً؟
Oh! What about him?!
صحيح! ماذا عنه؟
Who's "him"?
عنه؟
Oh, come on!
تعرفين
Those two guys who tried to pick us up at the coffee shop that one Sunday!
!الاثنان اللذان تقرّبا منا في المقهى يوم الأحد
Remember?
ألا تذكرين؟
They said they were both medical students at Beika University!
!قالا أنّهما طالبان في كليّة الطب في جامعة بيكا
Especially Minagawa-san! He's totally cool!
!ميناغاوا-سان تحديداً! إنّه رائع جدّاً
The other one was Wakamatsu-san, was it?
الآخر كان واكاماتسو-سان، صحيح؟
He's perfect for you, Ran!
!إنّه مثالي لك يا ران
He seemed really interested in you, after all!
فكان مهتماً بك وفقما بدا
Hello there, Ran-san! I've been looking for you!
!مرحباً يا ران-سان! كنت أبحث عنك
What good timing!
!توقيت ممتاز
Don't you agree?
صحيح؟
We'll solve any case at all, no matter how difficult it may be!
!سنحلّ أيّ قضية مهما كانت صعوبتها
If you have any problems, just leave it to us!
!إن كانت لديكم أيّ مشاكل، فاتركوها لنا
Conan! Stop loafing around and help!
!كونان! توقف عن الكسل وساعدنا
I'm high school detective Shinichi Kudo!
أنا مُتحرّي الثانوية كودو شينتشي
I'm not about to play games with a bunch of pipsqueaks!
لا وقت لديّ لألعب مع أطفال
Ran!
ران
Ran-san! I'm here today to ask you something important!
ران-سان، أتيتُ اليوم لأطلب منك شيئاً مهماً
Ran-san!
!ران-سان
I'm here to ask you on a date!
أتيتُ لدعوتك في موعد
Date?!
!مـ-موعد؟
Would you come with me to tomorrow's Valentine party?
هلّا رافقتني لحفلة فالنتاين الغد؟
Valentine party?
حفلة فالنتاين؟
Yes. Girls are supposed to give chocolate to a boy they like,
أجل، يُفترض للفتاة أن تعطي شوكولاتة للفتى الذي يعجبها
and if the boy feels the same way for her,
،وإن كان يبادلها الشعور
he will eat the chocolate right there on the spot.
يأكل الشوكولاتة في لحظتها
Say, will Minagawa-san be coming too?
إذاً، هل سيأتي ميناغاوا-سان أيضاً؟
Of course. The party is taking place at his house, after all.
بالطبع، فالحفلة في منزله
We'll come! Ran and I will both come for sure!
!سنذهب! سأذهب وران معاً حتماً
Sonoko!
!سونوكو
R-Really?!
!حـ-حقاً؟
This is great! Thank you very much!
!رائع! شكراً لكما
Valentine party? Gimme a break.
حفلة فالنتاين؟ يا للهراء
Well then, I will come pick you up tomorrow.
سآتي لأخذكما غداً إذاً
Bye!
!وداعاً
Why did you say that without asking me?!
!لمَ قلتِ ذلك دون استشارتي؟
I guess I was right after all.
كما ظننت
You like Shinichi-kun, don't you?
أنتِ تحبين شينتشي-كن، صحيح؟
You're being faithful to him
تخلصين له
and giving all other guys the old "no thank you" routine!
"وتعطين بقية الشبّان معاملة "كلا، شكراً لك
Don't be stupid! Who would actually like that big mystery geek?!
لا تكوني حمقاء! من قد يُحب !مهووس التحرّي ذاك؟
Well excuse me.
أعتذر لذلك
Then you'll go to the Valentine party, right?
ستذهبين إذاً لحفلة الفالنتاين، صحيح؟
Of course I'll go!
!بالطبع
Alright! It's decided!
!رائع! حُسم الأمر
Just you watch, Katsuhiko Minagawa!
!شاهد فقط يا ميناغاوا كاتسوهيكو
I'll use my chocolate to melt even your bone marrow!
سأستعمل الشوكولاتة خاصتي لأذيب !حتّى نخاع عظامك
Sonoko has a new obsession...
...سـ-سونوكو تشتعل
I'm the great detective Kogoro Mori...
...أنا المتحرّي العظيم موري كوغورو
What are you doing, Ran?
ما الذي تفعلينه يا ران-نيتشان؟
Nothing much...
لا شيء مهم
It smells like chocolate!
!هذه رائحة شوكولاتة
Tomorrow's Valentine's Day!
غداً يوم الفالنتاين
You have someone to give chocolate to then?
هناك من تعطينه الشوكولاتة إذاً؟
How rude!
!يا للفظاظة
I wouldn't be making chocolate by hand if I didn't have someone to give any to!
لم أكن لأعدّ شوكولاتة إن لم يكن هناك من أعطيه
Oh, right! Who knows, Shinichi might just come back!
صحيح، قد يعود شينتشي-نيتشان
Shinichi?
شينتشي؟
Now that I think about it, there was a guy by that name...
صحيح كان هناك شخص بهذا الاسم
Hey, now.
لحظة، لحظة
I'm going now!
سأغادر الآن
OK. Go and catch a rich man.
اذهبي واصطادي رجلاً ثرياً
That's weird. Conan-kun isn't here either.
هذا غريب، كونان-كن ليس هنا أيضاً
Ran! What're you doing?!
ما الذي تفعلينه يا ران؟
We're about to leave without you!
!سنغادر دونك
I have no choice but to find out where that chocolate winds up!
!لا خيار أمامي سوى معرفة مقصد تلك الشوكولاتة
Sorry to keep you waiting!
!آسفة على التأخير
And away we go!
!انطلاق
Cheers!
!نخبكم
Now then, let us introduce our Beika University tennis club
لنبدأ إذاً بتقديم أعضاء نادينا للتنس بجامعة بيكا
to our guests, Ran Mori-san and Sonoko Suzuki-san!
لضيفتينا، موري ران-سان وسوزوكي سونوكو-سان
You go first, Minagawa!
أنت أولاً يا ميناغاوا
OK. I'm Katsuhiko Minagawa, the captain.
حسناً، أنا الكابتن ميناغاوا كاتسوهيكو
I'm happy to meet you two.
يسرّني لقاؤكما
Really?!
!حقّاً؟
I'm happy too!
!يسرني ذلك أيضاً
Calm down, calm down...
حسناً، حسناً، لنهدأ
I'm Kaori Sekiya.
أنا سيكيا كاوري
Sonoko-san. You're still young, but you shouldn't go overboard like that...
أنتِ صغيرة يا سونوكو-سان لذا لا تندفعي هكذا
She's envious of me.
إنّها تغار مني
She's really pretty but obviously really jealous too...
تتمتع بالجمال لكن غيورة جدّاً مع ذلك
Naomichi. You're next.
دورك تالياً يا ناوميتشي
Come on. You really are gloomy, you know that?
يا إلهي، أنت عبوس حقّاً
I'm Yoshimi Watanabe. Nice to meet you.
أنا واتانابي يوشيمي، سررت بلقائكما
And then there's me,
وأنا أخيراً
the strong, yet sensitive, Toshihide Wakamatsu!
،القويّ، لكن المرهف ولطيف الإحساس !واكاماتسو توشيهيدي
Who does Ran think she is?
ما خطب ران؟
She actually looks like she's having fun.
إنها تتسلى حقّاً
I'm sorry for the wait!
أعتذر على الإطالة
Here is today's main dish!
ها هو طبق اليوم الرئيسي
Thank you ever so much, Mrs. Minagawa!
!شكراً لك يا عمّة
You're Minagawa-san's mother?!
!أنتِ أم ميناغاوا-سان؟
You're so young!
!شابة
You certainly know how to flatter a woman!
!تجيدين اختيار الكلمات
Hey, lady! Let's play together!
!آنسة! لنلعب معاً
Susumu! Go to your room! You're disruptin' the party!
!سوسومو! اذهب لغرفتك! أنت تفسد الحفلة
You're Minagawa-san's younger brother?
أنت أخو ميناغاوا-سان الصغير؟
You're so cute!
!ظريف
But he doesn't really look like Minagawa-san, does he?
لكنه لا يشبهك حقاً، صحيح؟
How long is that stupid Ran going to be here?!
!إلى متى ستتركني ران هنا؟
I'm so cold and hungry!
!أشعر بالبرد والجوع
Oh no!
!تبّاً
Conan-kun! What are you doing here?!
!كونان-كن! ماذا تفعل هنا؟
I was just going to a friend's house but then I got lost!
!كنتُ في طريقي لمنزل صديق، لكن تهت
Do you know that boy?
أتعرفين ذاك الفتى؟
Yes. He's been staying at my house lately for certain reasons.
أ-أجل، يسكن في منزلنا مؤخراً لظروف ما
It must be cold outside. Come in.
الجوّ بارد خارجاً، ادخل
OK!
!حاضر
I think someone should perform something.
حسناً، أظن على أحد تقديم عرض الآن
Naomichi! You do it!
ناوميتشي، ابدأ أنت
You not hear me or something?! Get this party started!
!ألم تسمعني يا ناوميتشي؟! ارفع إيقاع هذه الحفلة
I'm not very good at that sort of thing.
لستُ بارعاً في هذه الأشياء
What?! You dare defy me?!
!ماذا؟ أترفض الإصغاء لكلامي؟
Just looking at your face makes me sick!
مجرّد النظر لوجهك يشعرني بالغثيان
Don't you think Minagawa-san's got a bit of an attitude problem?
ألا يعاني ميناغاوا-سان من مشكلة في سلوكه؟
It's good for guys to be a little like that!
يليق بالفتيان أن يكونوا هكذا قليلاً
Anyway, did you bring your chocolate?!
على أي حال، هل أحضرتِ الشوكولاتة؟
Yeah...
أجل
Watch! Minagawa-san's down for the count once he eats my chocolate!
انظروا فقط! سيسقط ميناغاوا-سان !بمجرد أكله للشوكولاتة خاصتي
You sure you didn't put poison in it then?
أوضعتِ بها سمّاً؟
I, Sonoko Suzuki, humbly offer--
...سأقدّم أنا سوزوكي سونوكو
Say, beautiful girls like you
إذاً، لا بدّ أن الفتيات الجميلات مثلك يا ران-سان
must have hobbies like tea ceremony and flower arrangement, right?
يمتلكن هوايات مثل مراسم الشاي وترتيب الأزهار، صحيح؟
Karate.
الكاراتيه
How could Ran-san do anything so uncivilized?!
كيف تمارس ران-سان شيئاً همجياً كهذا؟
As if such a lovely and charming woman would ever be into karate!
!مُحال لامرأة جميلة وفاتنة أن تهوى الكاراتيه
Kaori.
كاوري
Stop treating Naomichi like that.
كفّ عن معاملة ناوميتشي بذاك الأسلوب
It really pisses me off when you feel sorrier for him than me!
يغيظني عندما تأسفين عليه أكثر مني
You mean to say you're worse off than him?
أتقصد أنّك أسوأ حالاً؟
What?!
ماذا؟
You've changed!
لقد تغيّرت
You've become so reckless ever since then!
أصبحت متهوراً مذ آنذاك
What do you know?!
!ما الذي تعرفينه؟
I know enough! We grew up together, after all!
!أعرف! فقد كبرنا معاً
Get a hold of yourself!
!تمالك نفسك
Will you accept this?
هل ستقبل هذه؟
Knock it off. I only want to be friends.
توقفي، أريد أن نبقى أصدقاءً فقط
I see...
...هكذا إذاً
I guess you really do like Yoshimi the best...
...يوشيمي إذاً هي من
What's the matter?
ما الخطب؟
It should be OK, right? It's just her hand...
...لا بأس، صحيح؟ فهي يدها فقط
Here goes!
!حسنٌ
I have to take the initiative!
!عليّ القيام بالخطوة الأولى
What lovely hands...
...يا لليدين الجميلتين
Ran-san!
!ران-سان
Outta the way!
!ابتعد
Conan-kun!
!كونان-كن
R-Ran-san!
!ران-سان
Yes?
أجل؟
Take that!
!ابتعد عنها
Freakin' kid!
!أيّها الوغد
Stay away from Ran!
!لا تقترب من ران-نيتشان
Conan-kun!
كونان-كن؟
Susumu! How many times do I have to tell you?!
سوسومو! كم مرّة عليّ إخبارك؟
No sweets! Your cavity still hasn't healed yet!
!لا حلويات! لم يُشف تسوسك بعد
But Kaori gave it to me!
لكنّ كاوري-نيتشان أعطتني إياها
Kaori.
كاوري
It was Katsuhiko, wasn't it?!
كان كاتسوهيكو، صحيح؟
Did he do something bad to you?
أساء لك بشيء ما، صحيح؟
It's none of your business!
!الأمر لا يخصك
Katsuhiko's nothing but human scum!
!كاتسوهيكو مجرد حثالة
There's no reason for him to hurt you like that, no matter what!
لا سبب ليؤذيك هكذا مهما كان الأمر
Just leave me alone!
!دعني وشأني فقط
Damn that Katsuhiko!
!كاتسوهيكو الوغد
Katsuhiko! It's 10 years too soon for you to challenge me!
تنقصك 10 سنين لتتحداني يا كاتسوهيكو
Ran-san must be sick of being with a guy with muscle for brains.
لا بد أنّ مرافقة كتلة عضلات فارغة العقل مثله تضنيك يا ران-سان
Minagawa! Are you lookin' for a fight?!
!ميناغاوا! أتريد الشجار؟
I just call it like I see it.
أقول الواقع فقط
What?!
!ماذا؟
You're always like this!
!أنت هكذا دائماً
Why not think about other people's feelings for once?!
!لمَ لا تراعي مشاعر الآخرين قليلاً؟
You mean you have feelings too?
أي أن لديك مشاعر؟
Why, you...
!أيّها الوغد
Now, now, that's enough!
حسناً، حسناً، يكفي شجاراً
How about something to work off that alcohol?
ما رأيكم بتهدئة آثار الشراب قليلاً؟
Let go!
!دعني
Say, Katsuhiko...
...كاتسوهيكو
What?! You gonna lecture me too?!
!ماذا؟! هل ستعظينني أيضاً؟
Now then, let's all have dessert!
!حسناً، لنتناول التحلية جميعاً
Ah, here it is! Mrs. Minagawa's home-made cakes!
!كنتُ بانتظاره! كعك أم ميناغاوا المنزلي
I hope you like them...
آمل أن ينال إعجابكم
Of course I will! Thank you!
!بالطبع! شكراً جزيلاً
Say, is that cake good?
هل تلك الكعكة لذيذة يا آنسة؟
Both the cake and the coffee are great!
أجل، الكعكة والقهوة لذيذة أيضاً
Bitter!
!مُرّة
Don't drink her coffee!
لا تشرب كأسها
Here! Have some cake!
هاك، تناول كعكاً
Katsuhiko. Aren't you going to eat your cake?
لن تأكل كعكتك يا كاتسوهيكو؟
No. I hate sweets.
كلا، أكره الحلويات
Don't you think maybe you're smoking too much?
ألا ترى أنك تدخن بإسراف؟
You should try to cut back a little.
عليك التخفيف
Get off my case and quit annoyin' me!
!اخرسي! لا تنفكين تزعجينني
Looks like I got a little drunk.
يبدو أنّي ثملت قليلاً
Think I'll go get some fresh air.
سأذهب لتنشق هواء طلق
Empty.
فارغة
You can have mine.
يمكنك أخذ سجائري
Yoshimi likes him after all...
يوشيمي معجبة به حقّاً
What does she see in him, I wonder?
ما الجذّاب في رجل مثله؟
Which reminds me, do you have any chocolate for me, Ran-san?
بالمناسبة، ألديك أيّ شوكولاتة لي يا ران-سان؟
It's Katsuhiko! He's...
...كاتسوهيكو! إنّه
K-Katsuhiko! Katsuhiko!
!كاتسوهيكو! كاتسوهيكو
Katsuhiko!
!كاتسوهيكو
Call for the police and an ambulance!
!اتصلي بالشرطة والإسعاف
Right!
أجل
Katsuhiko!
!كاتسوهيكو
Mrs. Minagawa...
...عمّة
Katsuhiko-san passed away earlier.
فارق كاتسوهيكو-سان الحياة قبل قليل
The cause appears to be agricultural chemicals used as food poison.
سبب الوفاة مواد كيميائية زراعية اُستعملت كسمّ طعام كما يبدو
Yoshimi Watanabe-san.
واتانابي يوشيمي-سان
He collapsed shortly after eating your chocolate, did he not?
سقط بعدما أكل الشوكولاتة خاصتك بلحظات، صحيح؟
Yes.
أجل
It goes without saying that this case is an easy one.
إنّها قضية سهلة كما يبدو
What are you doing here?!
!ماذا تفعل هنا؟
I, the great detective Kogoro Mori, hastened to the scene!
!وسارعت، المتحري العظيم موري كوغورو، لمسرح الجريمة
You did it!
!الفاعل... هو أنت
You poisoned the chocolate in order to kill the victim!
!وضعتِ سمّاً في الشوكولاتة لقتل الضحية
Romantic issues were your motive!
!الدافع كان عاطفياً
All we have to do is check the rest of your chocolate to prove it!
!كلّ ما علينا هو التحقق من بقايا الشوكولاتة للإثبات
No! It wasn't me!
!كلا! لم تكن أنا! لم تكن أنا
Yoshimi!
!يوشيمي
Everything's too convenient for it to have been her.
لا يُعقل أن تكون جريمةً بسيطة بحيث تكون هي القاتلة
Everyone's eaten the exact same things as the victim.
أكل الجميع نفس الطعام مع الضحية
Even if the sushi was poisoned,
حتّى لو كان السوشي مسمماً
it would be impossible to tell which ones the victim would eat.
يستحيل معرفة أيّ ما سيأكله الضحية بالضبط
Everyone drank coffee that came from the same pot.
شرب الجميع القهوة من نفس الإبريق
Which means it was the cake?
مما يترك... الكعكة؟
No, the victim didn't eat it!
كلا، لم يأكلها الضحية
No. I hate sweets.
كلا، أكره الحلويات
What does it all mean?
ما معنى هذا؟
Was Yoshimi-san the murderer after all?!
أكانت يوشيمي-سان القاتلة بالفعل؟
That's it!
!هـ-ها هي
Mister!
!عمّ
Come to think of it,
كان هناك عقاب سجائر
there was a cigarette butt at the crime scene, wasn't there?
في مسرح الجريمة، صحيح؟
A cigarette?
سجائر؟
That's right! That's a possibility too!
!صحيح! ذلك احتمال أيضاً
So this is the cigarette butt discovered at the scene of the crime.
هذا عقب لفافة التدخين المتروكة في مسرح الجريمة إذاً
Yes, there are ways to poison cigarettes...
صحيح، هناك طرق لتسميم السجائر
I saw it! When Minagawa-san went outside,
شهدتُ الأمر! عندما خرج ميناغاوا-سان
Naomichi-san gave him his cigarettes!
!أعطاه ناوميتشي-سان سجائره
N-Naomichi! How could you?!
...نا-ناوميتشي؟ أيمكن أنّك
Well?!
!أجب
We can always find out if we examine the cigarette butt, you know!
!يمكننا المعرفة إن حلّلنا عقب اللفافة
It's true! I did it!
!صـ-صحيح! أنا فعلتها
I've hated him for a long time!
!كنتُ أبغضه لوقت طويل
That damn Katsuhiko was always making a fool of me!
!كاتسوهيكو اللعين كان يسخر مني دائماً
He even hurt Kaori!
!آذى كاوري فوق ذلك
So I put poison in the cigarette filter!
لذا سمّمتُ مُرشِّح السجائر
The filter?
مُرشِّح؟
No! He didn't do it!
كلا، ليس هو المجرم
Mommy! My tooth hurts!
!أمّي! ضرسي يؤلمني
She's washing the coffee cups.
تغسل أكواب القهوة
At a time like this?
في وقت كهذا؟
That's it! I got it!
!هكذا إذاً، وجدتُها
Here goes!
حسنٌ
I call this the Anesthetic Watch Gun.
أسمّيه مسدس ساعة التخدير
With it, you can make anyone within close range go to sleep instantly.
يمكنك تنويم أيّ شخص في مدى قريب فورياً
His voice was Number 59, if I remember correctly...
...كان صوته رقم 59 كما أتذكر
One moment, please, Inspector Megure.
لحظة من فضلك حضرة المفتّش
He is not the murderer.
ليس القاتل
What are you talking about? He's confessed to it, you know.
!ما الذي تقوله؟ اعترف بنفسه
He did indeed plan to murder the victim, but he failed.
نوى ارتكاب الجريمة حقّاً، لكنه فشل
Have a look at the cigarette butt.
انظر لعقب اللفافة
All of the victim's other cigarettes in the house were unfiltered.
كانت كلّ سجائر الضحية الأخرى في المنزل بلا مُرشّح
After receiving the cigarettes from Naomichi,
بعد أخذه السجائر من ناوميتشي
the victim removed the filter before lighting one up.
أزال الضحية المُرشِّح قبل إشعالها كالمعتاد
In other words, he didn't smoke the part that had the poison in it.
أي أنّه لم يدخن الجزء المسموم
Then who did it, Dad?!
من كان الفاعل إذاً يا أبي؟
The real murderer was...
...الفاعل الحقيقي
...you, Katsuhiko-kun's mother!
كان أمّ كاتسوهيكو-كن
What are you talking about?!
!ما-ما الذي تقوله؟
How in the world could I have done it?!
!كيف قتلته بالضبط؟
By poisoning the food.
بتسميم الطعام
Everyone ate the same food!
!أكل الجميع الطعام نفسه
Yes. But only Katsuhiko-kun died.
صحيح، لكن كاتسوهيكو فقط مات
He died because he didn't eat.
مات لأنّه لم يأكل
What do you mean, he didn't eat?
ما قصدك لأنّه لم يأكل؟
Mrs. Minagawa.
أيّتها العمة
I hear you were nearly red with anger
سمعت أنّك استشطتِ غضباً
when Susumu-kun ate some chocolate.
.عندما أكل سوسومو-كن شوكولاتة
Yet you let him have some cake!
مع ذلك تركته يأكل كعكاً
Why was that?
لمَ ذلك؟
It was because you put poison in the coffee
لأنّك وضعتِ سمّاً في القهوة
and the antidote in the cake!
وترياقاً في الكعك
Seeing Susumu-kun drink the poisoned coffee,
بعد رؤية سوسومو-كن يشرب القهوة
you rushed to give him some of the cake and the antidote!
هرعتِ لإعطائه كعكاً، أيّ الترياق
You knew that Katsuhiko-kun probably wouldn't eat the cake
كنتِ تعرفين أنّ كاتسوهيكو لن يأكل الكعك
since he hated sweets.
لأنّه يكره الحلويات
Then, upon devising this plan,
وبعد تفكيرك بالخطّة
you decided to use the fact that Yoshimi-san loved him to your advantage!
قررتِ استغلال حبّه ليوشيمي-سان لصالحك
You knew without question that he would eat her chocolate.
عرفتِ أنّه سيأكل الشوكولاتة منها حتماً
Being the very first person on the scene,
كنتِ أوّل من وصل للجثة
you took the chocolate he partially ate
وأخذتِ الشوكولاتة التي قضم منها
and replaced it with poisoned chocolate!
واستبدلتها بالمسمومة
All while trying to make Yoshimi-san look guilty, of course.
بمحاولة إلقاء التهمة على يوشيمي-سان بالطبع
Pure fiction! There's no proof!
!مجرد خيال! لا دليل لديك
But there is. In the coffee cups.
الدليل موجود، في أكواب القهوة
Before the police came, you washed the coffee cups as quickly as possible.
غسلتِ الأكواب قبل قدوم الشرطة بأسرع ما يمكنك
No matter how much you washed them,
مهما غسلتِها من مرّات
detailed examination will still find the poison!
سيجد الفحص الدقيق آثار السم
Even if there isn't any left in the cups,
حتى لو لم يبق منه في الأكواب
there will still be some in the drain pipes.
سنجدها في أنابيب التصريف
Mrs. Minagawa.
عمّة
It appears it's starting to melt.
يبدو أنّها بدأت تذوب
Yoshimi-san's real chocolate bar, which you hid in your kimono, that is.
شوكولاتة يوشيمي-سان الحقيقية التي خبّأتها في ثوب الكيمونو
Nonsense!
!هراء
How would I know that he would eat Yoshimi's chocolate?!
!كيف لي أن أعرف أنّه سيأكل شوكولاتة يوشيمي-سان؟
Why would I kill my own son?!
!لمَ قد أقتل ابني؟
No! Katsuhiko's real parents died 7 years ago in an accident!
كلا! مات والدا كاتسوهيكو الحقيقيان قبل 7 أعوام في حادث
Then you, his father's sister, took him in!
ثم تبنيته أنت، أخت أبيه
Katsuhiko liked Yoshimi because she looked like his real mother.
كان كاتسوهيكو معجباً بيوشيمي لأنّها بدت كأمه الحقيقية
That's how you knew for sure that he would eat her chocolate!
!لذا كنتِ على يقين أنه سيأكل الشوكولاتة خاصتها
I'm so sorry, Yoshimi-san!
!آسفة يا يوشيمي-سان
I just happened to see you buying chocolate one day
رأيتك صدفةً تشترين شوكولاتة في أحد الأيام
and then the idea suddenly came to me!
!فخطرت لي الفكرة
I had no other choice!
لم يكن لديّ خيار
We desperately needed Katsuhiko's inheritance
كنّا بحاجة ماسة لإرث كاتسوهيكو-كن
because my husband's business went under!
!لفشل تجارة زوجي
I wanted to protect this house and Susumu's happiness!
!أردتُ حماية هذا المنزل وسعادة سوسومو
A lot sure happened today...
كان يوماً حافلاً
What should I do with this chocolate now?
ماذا أفعل بهذه الشوكولاتة الآن؟
Ran-san! Here you are!
!ران-سان! كنتِ هنا
I could give you a ride home if you want...
يمكنني أن أقلّك للبيت إن طلبتِ
No, that's okay...
كلا، لا داعي
Oh! Is that chocolate for me?!
!أهذه الشوكولاتة لي؟
No--
...كلا
Thank you! I'm utterly delighted!
!شكراً جزيلاً! أشعر بالسرور
That's enough!
!يكفي
Just leave me alone!
!دعني وشأني
I'm sorry for bothering you!
!المعذرة
For Shinichi-kun
لشينتشي-كن
Ran...
ران
You can eat it if you'd like.
يمكنك أكلها إن أردت
I'm sure Shinichi wouldn't mind either.
فلن يمانع شينتشي حتماً
You followed me to keep me safe, right?
تبعتني لحمايتي، صحيح؟
Thanks!
شكراً
Sending 25 million yen along with toys seems too much to be a prank.
إرسال 25 مليون ين مع ألعاب يبدو كثيراً بالنسبة لمقلب
And that letter... What does it say they're coming for?!
كما تلك الرسالة... ما المقصود بأنه قادم لأجله؟
Great work, Shinichi!
كما يُتوقع منك يا شينتشي
It was nothing--
...لم يكن
On the next Conan--
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
The Threatening Monthly Presents.
هدايا التهديد الشهرية
Next Conan's Hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Barcode.
شفرة تعرّف
Don't miss the next episode
قضيّة الحلقة القادمة صعبة قليلاً